{
  "main": {
    "question1": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 100,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What describes you best?",
        "answertext": "Im thinking about nursing school",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 100,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": -500,
        "medass": -500,
        "medadmin": -500,
        "healthinfo": -500,
        "healthsci": -500,
        "questiontext": "What describes you best?",
        "answertext": "Im in nursing school",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": -100,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What describes you best?",
        "answertext": "Im a nurse",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": -500,
        "bsn": -500,
        "msn": -500,
        "np": -500,
        "dnp": -500,
        "mc": 500,
        "medass": 500,
        "medadmin": 500,
        "healthinfo": 500,
        "healthsci": 500,
        "questiontext": "What describes you best?",
        "answertext": "im interested in supporting nurse roles like administration and assisting roles",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question2": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 200,
        "bsn": 200,
        "msn": 200,
        "np": 200,
        "dnp": 200,
        "mc": 200,
        "medass": 200,
        "medadmin": 200,
        "healthinfo": 200,
        "healthsci": 200,
        "questiontext": "When do you want to start school?",
        "answertext": "1-3 Months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 150,
        "bsn": 150,
        "msn": 150,
        "np": 150,
        "dnp": 150,
        "mc": 150,
        "medass": 150,
        "medadmin": 150,
        "healthinfo": 150,
        "healthsci": 150,
        "questiontext": "When do you want to start school?",
        "answertext": "4-6 Months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 100,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "When do you want to start school?",
        "answertext": "7-12 Months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 50,
        "bsn": 50,
        "msn": 50,
        "np": 50,
        "dnp": 50,
        "mc": 50,
        "medass": 50,
        "medadmin": 50,
        "healthinfo": 50,
        "healthsci": 50,
        "questiontext": "When do you want to start school?",
        "answertext": "1 year+",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question3": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": -1000,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What degree do you have or are currently pursuing?",
        "answertext": "RN",
        "questionamount": 5
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": -1000,
        "bsn": -1000,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What degree do you have or are currently pursuing?",
        "answertext": "BSN",
        "questionamount": 5
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": -1000,
        "bsn": -1000,
        "msn": -1000,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What degree do you have or are currently pursuing?",
        "answertext": "MSN",
        "questionamount": 5
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": -1000,
        "bsn": -1000,
        "msn": -1000,
        "np": -1000,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What degree do you have or are currently pursuing?",
        "answertext": "NP",
        "questionamount": 5
      },
      "answer5": {
        "rn": 500,
        "bsn": 500,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What degree do you have or are currently pursuing?",
        "answertext": "None of the above",
        "questionamount": 5
      }
    },
    "question3a": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What is your highest completed education?",
        "answertext": "Some high school",
        "questionamount": 3
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What is your highest completed education?",
        "answertext": "High school graduate",
        "questionamount": 3
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What is your highest completed education?",
        "answertext":"College",
        "questionamount": 3
      }
    },
    "question4": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": -500,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "Do you have an RN?",
        "answertext": "Yes",
        "questionamount": 2
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 500,
        "medadmin": 500,
        "healthinfo": 500,
        "healthsci": 500,
        "questiontext": "Do you have an RN?",
        "answertext": "No",
        "questionamount": 2
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "",
        "answertext": "",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "",
        "answertext": "",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question5": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": -500,
        "bsn": -500,
        "msn": -500,
        "np": -500,
        "dnp": -500,
        "mc": 500,
        "medass": 500,
        "medadmin": 500,
        "healthinfo": 500,
        "healthsci": 500,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "I'm interested in nursing, but I would lie to test the waters with a quicker-entry degree before committing to the field.",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": -500,
        "msn": -500,
        "np": -500,
        "dnp": -500,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "12 months - 18 months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "18 months - 2 years",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "2 - 4 Years",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question5a": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": -100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": -100,
        "healthsci": -100,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "6-8 months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": -100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": -100,
        "healthsci": -100,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "8-12 months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "13-18 months",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "How long can you commit to school?",
        "answertext": "18 months+",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question6": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What are you good at?",
        "answertext": "Strong Leader",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What are you good at?",
        "answertext": "Tech Savvy",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 100,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What are you good at?",
        "answertext": "Good communicator",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 0,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What are you good at?",
        "answertext": "Calm under pressure",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    },
    "question7": {
      "answer1": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What areas of work do you enjoy most?",
        "answertext": "Education",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer2": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 0,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 0,
        "healthsci": 0,
        "questiontext": "What areas of work do you enjoy most?",
        "answertext": "Family",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer3": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 0,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 0,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 100,
        "medass": 0,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 200,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What areas of work do you enjoy most?",
        "answertext": "Research and Tech",
        "questionamount": 4
      },
      "answer4": {
        "rn": 0,
        "bsn": 100,
        "msn": 100,
        "np": 100,
        "dnp": 100,
        "mc": 0,
        "medass": 100,
        "medadmin": 0,
        "healthinfo": 100,
        "healthsci": 100,
        "questiontext": "What areas of work do you enjoy most?",
        "answertext": "Patient Care",
        "questionamount": 4
      }
    }
  }
}
